翻譯: vince 奇跡道長 sumsmit
噢 我真是累死了
Oh! I'm so exhausted.
今天我在跑步機上
Today on the treadmill,
一邊睡一邊跑了四分之一里的路
I actually fell asleep for a quarter mile.
校對: 不賣萌斯基
你昨晚又說夢話了
You were talking in your sleep again last night.
是的 因為那些新藥 怎么不能有酷的副作用呢
Yeah, it's these new meds. Why can't they have cool side effects?
后期: 怪查理
什么樣的是酷的副作用
What would be a cool side effect?
不知道 變身"潛水俠"那種吧
I don't know. Anything Aquaman does.
壓制: ＢＢ
噢 你穿了那件T恤
Oh, you're wearing that t-shirt.
我以為會換個睡衣啥的
I thought you were gonna swap it out for a nightie,
- 緊身的那種 - 那種太復雜了
- something tight. - That's so complicated.
這衣服很難看出來正反面
It's hard tell what's the front and what's the back,
其他部分也清清楚楚的
or where everything is so clear about this shirt.
頭從這兒進 胳膊這兒進
My head goes here; my arms go here...
而且你總用衣擺擦干手 很性感哦
And you wipe your hands here, which is hot.
干凈的手很性感
Clean hands are hot.
- 爸媽 我們要談談 - 談談敲門的重要性么
- Parents, we need to talk. - Talk or knock?
我明天有個客人要來
I have someone coming over tomorrow,
我要聲明一下
and not that it should matter,
這個客人是女同
but this someone happens to be a lesbian.
Reese剛來學校 她需要我這個朋友
Reese is new at school, and she needs me as a friend.
我碰巧就以多元化的朋友圈出名
I'm kind of known for having a diverse crew
我不會隨便給別人貼標簽
that doesn't pigeonhole people,
除了那些肌肉棒子 話劇呆子 刻薄妹子
unlike the jocks, the drama nerds, the mean girls,
還有那些怪胎...
the freaks with the weird...
你們千萬別給我添亂子
I really don't want you guys to blow this for me.
就是說不許說關于女同的笑話
So that means no lesbian jokes.
我都不知道關于女同的笑話
I don't think I know a lesbian joke.
我知道一個 但不懂好笑在哪里
I know one lesbian joke, but I don't get it.
我們可以讓Eve那個朋友給我們解釋解釋
Well, I know, let's get Eve's lesbian friend to explain it to us.
你們能上網嗎 我貌似上不了網了
Are you guys online? I can't seem to get on the internet.
能啊 我們在載"快一點"
Yeah, we're downloading Quicken.
一款財務管理軟件
這個計算機笑話好 快給呆伯特投稿
Ha-ha-ha-ha, great computer joke. Somebody call Dilbert.
著名職場卡通人物
我都不知道我為什么要進來
It's like, I don't even know why I come in here.
- 我也是 - 什么
- Neither do I. - What?
給我出去
Get out now.
門鎖上了 沒人能進出了
This door is locked. No one comes in or out.
我快睡著了 就到二壘就好了吧
It's just I'm fading fast. So how about just top stuff.
也行
I'll take it.
- 感覺怎么樣 - 別撓我的腳了
- How's this? - Stop tickling my feet.
我都沒碰你的腳啊 親愛的
I'm nowhere near your feet, honey.
- 什么是二壘啊 - 我也快不知道了
- What's "Top stuff?" - I honestly don't even know anymore.
好了 肯定不會再有第四個孩子出現了
Okay, that's it. We're officially out of kids.
有沒有搞錯
Oh, come on.
樓上鄰居又覺得我們想聽他的電視了
The upstairs neighbor thinks we want to hear his TV again.
好吧 我去會會他
Okay, I'm gonna go up there.
可能是個用助聽器的老人
Probably some old guy with a hearing aid.
他會認出我是新聞臺的 我給他簽個名
He'll recognize me from the news, I'll sign an autograph,
然后我馬上回來 然后你竟然睡著了
and then I'll be right back down... and you're asleep.
我打賭"潛水俠"肯定沒碰到過這事
I bet this never happens to Aquaman.
你好
Excuse me.
- 哦對不起 - 哦
- Oh, sorry... uh... - Oh.
你不是老人家啊
Uh... you're not an old man.
又 見 彩 虹
第一季  第二集
電波誠譯
- 有什么事嗎 - 我是你樓下的鄰居
- What exactly are we doing here? - I'm your downstairs neighbor.
- 哦 嗨 - 首先呢
- Oh, hey. - So first of all...
歡迎入住 很高興能和你做鄰居
welcome to the building. Lovely to have you.
其次 雖然挺蠢的
Second of all, and this is dumb and so stupid.
說起來有些好笑
I feel funny even mentioning it,
- 但你電視有那么一點點響 - 哦天啊
- but your TV is just a skosh loud... - Oh, my god.
好了 我知道了 我馬上去關小聲一點
Oh, okay. You know what? I'm gonna turn it down.
進來吧
Come on in.
- 好的 我應該可以進去 - 我剛開那么響
- Okay, I'm allowed to do this. - I had it turned up
是因為我在廚房烤餅干
because I was baking cookies in the kitchen.
自從離婚后我就又重新開始烤餅干
I've gotten back into baking since my divorce.
我前夫不喜歡餅干
My ex didn't like cookies.
事實上 唯一比餅干更讓他討厭的是
Actually, the only thing he hated more than cookies
沒能和咖啡館的女吧員上床
was not sleeping with baristas.
不知道我為何跟你說這些 我叫Kelly
I don't know why I'm telling you this. I'm Kelly, by the way.
- 我是不是認識你啊 - 這個有印象嗎
- Do I know you from somewhere? - Does this ring a bell?
關注時事 紐約
Stay informed, New York.
- 沒有 - 我是Mike Henry
- No. - I'm Mike Henry.
我是個新聞主播 第四頻道 電視上的
I'm a newscaster, Channel 4... television.
我知道我怎么會認識你了
I know where I know you from.
我以前在86街的星巴克見過你
I used to see you at the starbucks on 86th street.
你是那個有著銳利的藍色眼睛的家伙
You're the guy with those piercing blue eyes.
我不知道它們算不算銳利吧
Well, I don't know if they pierce.
它們 確實能刺兩下
They, uh... maybe poke a little.
- 你也很幽默啊 - 我應該
- You're funny too. - Oh, well... I should...
我差不多該出去了
I should probably hit the old hallway.
等等 你走之前 先幫我嘗嘗餅干
Oh, wait. You know what? Before you go, I need a taster.
我可能多放了點香草
Now, I might have gone a little bit heavy with the vanilla,
而且肯定忘了開烤箱
and I definitely forgot to turn on the oven.
好吧 我一團糟
Okay, I'm a mess.
你就舔一下這個吧
You know what? Just lick this.
哇 這是巧克力片是吧
Oh, wow. That's chocolate chip, right?
我的意思是我沒吃到 但是 我
I mean, I didn't get one, but-but-but I...
我嘗到味道了 就是它了
I can taste them. That's... that all checks out.
我該走了 謝謝你
I-I-I should go. Um, thank you.
關注時事哦
Stay informed.
那個很好吃
Those are good.
這篇寫給<美國周刊>的文章我落下太多了
Ugh, I'm so behind on this article for Us Weekly.
如果它叫<美國月刊>我就有更多時間了
If it was called "Us Monthly," I'd have more time.
- <美國月刊> 新雜志么 - 什么 不
- Us Monthly? Is that a new magazine? - What? No.
- 你有在聽我說話嗎 - 這么脆 不太討巧啊 媽
- Are you even listening? - Crunchy? Swing and a miss, Mom.
那是給我有在上學的兒子準備的午餐好么
Hey, that's a school lunch for my son who goes to school...
- 好吧 我說到哪了 - 你說完了
- Okay, where was I? - Uh... wrapping up.
我喜歡和Annie聊天 她是個好的傾聽者
I like talking to Annie, 'cause she's a good listener,
但我覺得她好久沒好好聽我說話了 自從
but I feel like she hasn't really been there for me since...
Ian多少歲了來著
How old is Ian again?
我知道你太忙了沒時間聽我的事兒
I know you're too busy to hear my troubles.
我猜你很難想象在這骯臟城市里
I guess it's hard for you to imagine what it's like
一個自由職業的單身女人的生存之道
to be a single woman freelancing in this dirty town
試圖笑著渡過三十歲
trying to laugh and love my way through my 30s.
"城市里的卡洛琳"那樣吧 我給你這么高評價
Okay, Caroline in the City, I'm gonna give you that one
NBC90年代喜劇 講述一個在曼哈頓的單身女漫畫家
因為你答應了今天照顧Graham
because you promised to watch Graham today.
能讓我離開這臺電腦我啥都干
Anything to get me away from this laptop.
早餐吃三明治么
Sandwiches for breakfast?
它不是早餐 不是給你吃的
They're not for breakfast. They're not for you!
有沒有搞錯 我們一張Melissa Etheridge的CD都沒有
Really? We don't own one Melissa Etheridge CD?
八十年代美國激進搖滾女歌手 92年出柜
現在都奧巴馬社會了家里還這么死板
Well, I guess it's Obama's America everywhere but here.
-我們有兩張KD LANG的CD - 他是誰
- We have two K.D. Lang CDs. - Who's he?
加拿大女歌手 曾獲格萊美 已出柜
噢親愛的 你要多做些研究才行
Oh, honey, you've got to do your research.
你馬上有個女同過來做客了
You have a lesbian coming over.
噢 三明治
Oh, PB&J.
- 太脆了 - 好了 都別吃了
- Crunchy. - Okay, stop eating it.
親愛的 多謝你昨晚讓鄰居
Honey, thank you so much for getting the neighbor
調小了他的電視 他什么樣的
to turn down his TV last night. What's he like?
就鄰居那樣唄
Um, neighborly.
普通的鄰居 標準臉型標準身材
Just an average neighbor. Standard face and body.
她... 對了她是個女的
She... and she was a "She", by the way.
她是那種特容易讓人忘記的類型
She was otherwise totally forgettable.
哦 太脆了 你又做成這樣了 親愛的
Oh, crunchy. You did it again, honey.
- 沒有三明治么 - 家里沒面包了
- No sandwich? - We're out of bread.
親愛的 那個兒童防曬霜太差了
Sweetie, that kid stuff's terrible.
用我的防曬霜吧 是法國的哦
Use mine sunscreen. It's French.
我不知道現在的匯率是多少
I don't know what the current exchange rate is,
但是這肯定特別物超所值
but it's definitely worth it.
還灑的到處都是
And it exploded everywhere.
大概33到45刀打水漂了
There goes $33 to $45.
這日子真是越過越順了
This day just keeps getting better.
沒事的 你最近發生了這么多事
It's okay. You've got a lot going on.
謝謝關心 是有很多事
Thank you. I do have a lot going on.
我只是想跟我的嫂子說說
I was just trying to explain this to my sister-in-law,
- 但是她不懂 - 我覺得你
- but she doesn't get it. - Well, I think you are
正在做世界上最重要的工作
doing the most important job in the world.
那肯定是很重要的
Well, it's definitely up there.
沒人給我任何幫助
And I've done it with no help from anyone.
- 那孩子的爸爸呢 - Mike一點忙都沒幫
- Well, what about the boy's father? - Mike's no help.
他完全沒有支持我
He gives me zero support.
單身媽媽真是了不起 你是個英雄
Single mothers are amazing. You're a hero.
哦不 我不是
Oh, no. I'm not a...
英雄 我只是做任何單身媽媽該做的事
hero. I'm just doing what any other single mother would.
- 好了 別說我了 - 別傻了 我們聽著呢
- But enough about me. - Don't be silly. We're here for you.
我是覺得我該發泄發泄了
I do suppose I could vent a little.
如果你不介意的話能關掉你的手機嗎
If you don't mind turning off your cell phone,
我會很感激的
I'd really appreciate it.
我不知道為什么大家都看不起WNBA
I don't know why people are so down on the WNBA.
- 他們有嗎 - 沒有 也不應該有
- Are they? - No, and they shouldn't be.
我的意思我覺得它比真正的籃球更好看
I mean, I think it's even better than real basketball.
我指正常的籃球
I mean, normal bask...
我是說誰會想去看一堆臭男人嘛 對吧
I mean, who wants to watch a bunch of sweaty guys anyway, right?
我吃剩的chick-fil-a呢
What happened to my leftover chick-fil-a?
美國主打雞肉三明治的快餐店 公開反同
我放在冰箱了
I left it in the fridge.
某個包容性超高的人扔垃圾桶了
Some super tolerant person probably threw it in the trash
因為那個快餐公司充滿了仇恨
because that company is all about hate.
是的 恨干的沒味道的雞肉
Yeah, hating dry, flavorless chicken.
- 你好 我叫Ian - 我是Reese
- 'Sup. I'm Ian. - Reese.
- 我喜歡你這衣服 - 他本該在讀大學的
- Like the pieces. - Uh, he's supposed to be in college.
但是我離開大學選擇開始我自己的事業
But I left to start up my own start... up.
- 跟臉書那家伙一樣 - 是的
- Like the social network. - Exactly.
說的是臉書創始人馬克·扎克伯格 從哈佛輟學
你想讓誰在電影里演你呢
Who do you want to play you in the movie?
2010年大衛芬奇以扎克伯格創建臉書經歷為藍本拍攝電影<社交網絡>
好吧 時間到
Okay, time's up.
她不錯啊 她什么情況
She's cute. What's her deal?
相信我 她對你可沒意思
Trust me. She's not interested.
不是吧 我覺得挺來電的
I don't know. I was feeling a vibe.
說正事 是不是你把我的chick-fil-a扔了
Whoa, seriously, did you throw out my chick-fil-a?
就這幾天 在冰箱頂層
Recently? Is it on the top?
寶貝 今天就我們兩個了
Honey. We have the whole place to ourselves.
我買了點咖啡 好讓我們保持清醒
And I got us some coffee so we can stay awake.
深度烘焙的 你懂我的意思
Dark roast, if you know what I'm saying.
Dark roast 深烘焙的 適合喜歡濃厚口味的人 味道比較苦
我一直在想我們那個鄰居
I can't stop thinkin about our neighbor.
就那個長相普通容易被遺忘的那個
You know, the plain, forgettable one?
等下 對了 就是 那個電視開超大聲的
Oh, wait, yeah, right, the one with the loud TV.
我一直放不下 覺得我們剛開始不太友好
I feel bad, like we got off on the wrong foot.
我覺得我應該上樓去跟她道個歉
And I was thinking I should go upstairs and apologize...
嗨 Mike
Hey, Mike.
但是她卻反倒下樓來向我道歉了
But then she decided to come down here instead.
喝咖啡么
Coffee?
我該走了 我就是想來送這個給你們
I should be going. I just wanted to drop these off.
原來只要打開烤箱
Turns out that if you actually turn on the oven,
餅干就好了 最妙的是
you get cookies. And the best part is,
你都不用把它從勺子上舔下來
you don't have to lick them off a spoon.
看你胡言亂語的 真搞笑
Great nonsense talk. Really silly stuff.
那啥 感謝到訪
Well... thanks for coming by.
真高興見到你 Kelly
It was so nice to meet you, Kelly.
我也是 能在這樓里找到一個
You too. It'll be so awesome to have a nice,
- 貼心的朋友真好 - 是啊
- cool friend in the building. - Yeah.
Mike竟然沒有提到你
Shame on Mike for not mentioning you.
好的 玩的很開心 記得電視聲音關小點
Okay, good hang. Keep the TV down.
- 再見 - 再見
- Bye. - Bye.
好吧 她昨天晚上可不長這樣
Well, she looked different last night.
我是說 咱家這燈光實在是太給人加分了
I mean, you know, the light in here must be very flattering,
都是你啦 你在什么樣的燈光下都特漂亮
which a credit to you, because you look great in any light.
也許是因為你忙著舔她的勺子
Maybe you were so busy licking her spoon
都沒時間好好看看人家
that you couldn't get a good look.
我就隨便舔了一下 她需要點鼓勵
That was a pity lick. She needed a win.
那啥 要不是我清楚這事兒
You know, if I didn't know any better,
我肯定會說你動心了 Mike
I'd say that you have a little crush, Mike.
我可沒有動心
I don't have a crush.
說實話 我其實都已經完全把她給忘了
Honestly, I had completely forgotten about her.
哦 Kelly
Oh, Kelly.
Kelly 不要 我不能這樣 這可不對
Kelly, no, we can't. It's wrong.
- 那好吧 - 好吧 嗨 起來
- Okay. - Okay, wait. Wake up.
- Mike 快起來 - 怎么了
- Mike, wake up. - Wh-what?
你打我了 你剛剛打我么
You hit me. Did you hit me?
你睡覺說夢話喊Kelly
You were talking in your sleep about Kelly.
好像是剛開始還在反抗
Sounds like you put up quite a struggle...
然后沒一秒你就放棄抵抗跟她上床了
right up until you immediately had sex with her.
你知道的 這些藥物會讓人做惡夢的
You know, these meds give me crazy dreams.
我懂的 她漂亮 又風趣
I get it. She's cute, she's funny,
餅干香草放的有點多
a bit of a heavy hand with the vanilla,
但你就承認你對她有點意思吧
but just admit that you are attracted to her.
要是你對某個男的也有興趣了
Well, I suppose if you were attracted to a guy,
你會直話直說嗎
you'd just put that out there?
Matt Damon  Ben Affleck  Casey Affleck,
Matt Damon, Ben Affleck, Casey Affleck,
還有Wahlbergs 波士頓劇里的所有男演員
the Wahlbergs, pretty much whole Boston scene.
- 好吧 夠了 - Mike 得了吧
- Okay, enough. - Mike, come on.
我就是想讓你跟我說實話而已
I just want you to be honest with me.
我一直對你說實話
I am being honest with you.
我對Kelly沒有任何意思
I'm not attracted to Kelly.
好吧 那你愛夢啥
Fine. You dream about whatever you
就夢啥去吧 行了吧 我睡我的覺了
want to dream about, okay? I'm gonna get some sleep.
哦 Annie
Oh, Annie...
Annie 你如此漂亮 性感 還聰明
Annie, you're so beautiful and sexy and smart.
- 你真完美 - 好了吧 跟你說下
- You're the whole package. - Okay, just so you know,
你睡著的時候可不抖
when you asleep, you don't shake.
還有 你不會像鬼一樣說夢話
And also, you don't talk like a ghost.
我聽不到
I can't hear yoooouu.
Mike不就做了個跟別的女的春夢么
So Mike had a sexy dream about another woman.
Mike不跟我講實話 讓我很心煩
It just annoys me that Mike won't be honest.
如果他真跟你說實話 肯定會讓你把這T恤燒了
If he were really being honest, he'd tell you to burn that shirt.
怎么大家都對這T恤有意見
What does everybody have against this shirt?
我見過你拿它擦銀器
I've seen you polish silver with that.
我覺得也許你可以給你自己搞點小動作
I'm just saying maybe you could step up your game a little.
你說的對 這里沒擦到
You're right. I missed a spot.
記著 我們要找一身衣服透露著
So remember, we're going for an outfit that says,
"我對非傳統生活超沒意見"
"I'm cool with alternative lifestyles."
今天是不是可愛的Reese來啊
So is the lovely Reese coming today?
我不想把Axe身體噴霧劑浪費在家人身上
I don't want to waste my Axe body spray on just family.
你找錯對象了 這對象是個女同志
You're barking up the wrong tree. This tree is a lesbian.
如果Reese是女同志 那我就是大美女
If Reese is a lesbian, then I must be a pretty lady,
因為她肯定喜歡我 那我今天到底噴不噴啊
because she's definitely into me. So am I Axe-ing or not?
- 噴 - 別噴
- Axe-ing. - Not.
我絕對不會再帶Reese來這兒了
I'm never bringing Reese back here.
這地方就是尷尬的雷區
This place is a minefield of embarrassment.
-我們要去JJ游樂場 - 從J到Js
- We're going to JJ's funcade. - J to the Js.
飲食與游戲 愛死那兒了
Food and games. Love that place.
- 我也是 - 原來你們都在這兒啊
- Me too. - There's my little Graham cracker.
紅色鞋子 棕色褲子配黃色毛衣
Red shoes, brown pants, and yellow sweater?
你想裝扮成漢堡么
You trying to look like a hamburger?
上回照看你可把我樂壞了 兄弟
I had such a good time watching you the other day, bud.
我跟你家大人講有機會還帶你去公園玩
I told your folks I'd take you to the park again.
好吧 我只是想跟那些老媽們聊聊天
Okay, I just wanted to hang with those moms again.
她們賞識我的工作讓我感覺很好
It felt nice to be around people who appreciate what I do,
即使都是我編出來的
Even if it's just something I pretend to do.
我們這次還是去JJ游樂場吧
Let's go to JJ's funcade instead.
公園才是真的好玩
The park is nature's funcade.
公園里沒有獎品
The park doesn't have prizes.
那你就說錯了
Well, that's where you're wrong.
如果我們去公園 就給你喝蘇打水
If we go to the park, you win a soda.
我喜歡 我能不能用Twizzler棒棒糖喝啊
I like soda. Can I drink it through a twizzler?
Twizzler扭扭糖 一種兒童糖果 中通外直
只能用半根
Half a twizzler.
我覺得我肯定會是個好母親
I feel like I'd make a good mom.
就因為我夢到了她
And now just because I had a dream about her...
當時也沒告訴她我已婚了
and didn't tell her I was married...
還舔了下勺子 Annie就覺得我喜歡上她了
and licked a few spoons, Annie thinks I'm into her.
女人嘛
Women.
總是沒什么實際證據就亂下結論
Always jumping to conclusions based on overwhelming evidence.
我想到了 我想到了 我們四人約會吧
I got it. I got it. We'll double date.
我撮合你跟Kelly 到時候Annie就知道
I'll set you up with Kelly, and then Annie will know
我可沒覺得她火辣
that I don't find her attractive.
哦 等下 她不辣嗎
Oh, hold on. She's not attractive?
你要把我跟一個丑女撮合到一起嗎
You're trying to set me up with a jacked-up woman?
這可不行
Uh-uh. Oh, no.
一旦這話傳出去 我可就降低自己標準了
Word gets around town that I've lowered my standards,
我的股票一跌 妹子們就會喊 "賣出Harris"
my stock drops, ladies go, "Sell. Sell on Harris."
這就是經濟學
That's just economics.
相信我 她不會讓你跌的 絕對是抬價的
Trust me. She's sufficiently jacked. She's jacked exquisitely.
你答應來吃晚飯就行了
Just say you'll come to dinner.
好吧 她最好對得起觀眾 因為你看這張臉
Okay, but she better look good, because you see all this?
這張臉可輸不起
It's too big to fail.
你覺得他們會看出我們沒在工作嗎
You think they can tell we're not working?
哦 老天 這地方真太扯淡了
Oh, my god. This place is ridiculous.
- 你知道我們該干嘛么 - 可憐這些生靈嗎
- You know what we should do? - Pity the living?
還有 我們該告訴服務員今天是我生日
And... and we should tell the waiter that it's my birthday,
然后他們就會給我唱那首爛歌了
and then they'll have to do that lame song for me.
那不是你哥哥么
Is that your brother?
Ian 你來這兒干嘛
Ian, what are you doing here?
嗨 我正好在附近
Oh, hey. Oh, I was just in the neighborhood.
就想著進來看看這些老跳舞機
Thought I'd check out the old stomping grounds.
嗨 快看這位老姑娘
Hey, check out this old girl.
很好奇她還能不能跳舞 是否能像以前一樣
Wonder if she still dance, dances like she used to.
別 別 別這樣
No, no, no, no, no. Don't do this.
我幾乎都不記得怎么用這玩意兒了
I barely remember how to use this thing.
或者全都還記得
Or do I totally remember?
真抱歉 他就是想來這兒顯擺
I'm so sorry. He's trying to show off
因為他有點喜歡上了你
because he has a stupid crush on you.
沒關系的 他蠻好玩的
That's okay. This is hilarious.
- 是啊 確實 - 就好像 是機器在指揮我
- Yeah, totally. - It's, like, is the machine telling me
該做什么 或是我在指揮它
what to do, or am I telling it?
我只是想寫好<美國周刊>那篇文章
I just want to get this us weekly article right,
因為我去看醫生的時候老會看到它
because I'm going to be seeing it in my doctor's office
一看就是一年半載的
for the next year and a half.
說到這 你們碰到過那種特別有偏見的婦科醫生嗎
Speaking of, does anyone else have a super judge-y gyno?
- Leigh  Graham這樣正常嗎 - 我將永生
- Um, Leigh, is Graham okay? - I am forever!
沒事的 就是喝了點蘇打 吃了幾根Twizzlers棒棒糖
He's fine. He just had a few sodas and a couple twizzlers.
哇哦 那可是好多糖分啊
Wow! That's a lot of sugar.
我覺得我們說跑題了
I feel like we're getting off track here.
我從來都不會給Duncan吃加工過的食物
I never give Duncan anything processed.
這對個給孩子起名Duncan的媽媽也算了不起了
Pretty high almighty for a lady who named her son Duncan.
你們真的變了好多
You guys have really changed.
走吧 兒子 我們走
Come on son, we're leaving.
Graham 說你呢
Graham, that's you!
- Leigh 說你呢 - Graham 跑慢點
- Leigh, it's you! - Graham, slow down!
今天我沒穿對胸罩
I'm not wearing the right bra for this!
- 你看到Reese了沒 - 她在那邊
- Have you seen Reese? - She's over there.
*快樂 生日快樂 JJ全體員工祝你生日快樂*
*Happy, happy birthday From JJ's funcade crew.*
*快樂 生日快樂 我們祝你生日快樂*
*Happy, happy birthday from all of us to you.*
哦 上帝 你真是太壞了
Oh. Oh, god. You are awful.
你要承認你迷戀上了Kelly 我們就可以
We'd have a lot less dishes to do if you would just admit
少做不少菜了
that you have a crush on Kelly.
別說笑了 這可是個合法的四人約會
That's ridiculous. It's a legitimate double date.
他們看起來挺來電
They do seem to be hitting it off.
是的 可不是嗎
Yes, they do, don't they?
- 那是我們的小動作 - 啥
- That was our thing. - What?
沒啥
Nothing.
- 哦 - 面包時間
- Oh. - Bread time.
面包實行分餐制
Individual portions of
都別喂來喂去的了
bread that everyone can feed to themselves.
啊哦 帕金森又犯了
Oops, Parkinson's.
怎么了 帕金森啦
What? Parkinson's.
為啥你和Ian親熱
Why were you making out with Ian?
你看到了啊 抱歉 我知道他是你哥
Oh, you saw that? I'm sorry. I know he's your brother, and...
哥哥是小伙子嘛
Yeah, and... brothers are guys.
- 你是女同啊 - 哦 我不是
- You're a lesbian. - No, I'm not.
- 你確定 - 是 我確定
- Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm sure.
但是我聽說你在聚會上親了個女生
But I heard that you kissed a girl at a party.
是啊 只是因為男生喜歡這樣啊
Yeah, I did, but only 'cause guys love that.
嘿 游蕩空中的小丑魚
Hey, air swimmer clownfish.
- 沒啥大不了 - 我不敢相信
- No bigs. - I can't believe this.
讓我再多看看 不知怎么 你越看越美啊
Let me get some more of that. Somehow yours just seems better.
你們是一輩子的好朋友咯
So you guys have been friends forever.
是啊 從我們一起在奧蘭多打拼就是了
Oh, yeah, ever since we started out down in Orlando.
還記得我們報道 州長的的就職典禮
Remember when we covered the... Governor's inauguration?
對 Mike在州長辦公室安營扎寨
Yeah, Mike camped out in the Governor's office
說給我們個引用不然不走
and wouldn't leave until we got a quote.
然后你在印刷間和莎莎舞女鬼混被抓到
And you got caught in the press room with that salsa dancer.
等等 不對 是個雞尾酒女服務員
Or wait, no, that's wrong. It was a cocktail waitress.
真的很難記清啊 我肯定
It's hard to remember, I'm sure.
是啊 因為太多了
Yeah, because there's been so many.
我本想說 是因為時間太久了
I was gonna say because it was such a long time ago.
誰年輕的時候沒有瘋狂過
Everybody does crazy things when they're young.
但我現在是個紳士
But I'm a gentleman now.
我可不希望太紳士哦
Well, I hope not too much of a gentleman.
結果那個女服務員居然也是個"紳士"
Didn't that cocktail waitress turn out to be a gentleman
- 前后都是 - 你在搞什么
- in the end... and in the front? - What the hell are you doing?
要說就說清楚嘛 誰想看我的艾美獎
Just trying to be accurate. Who wants to see my Emmys?
別太興奮 只是日間艾美獎
Don't get too excited. They're daytime Emmys.
要說就說清楚嘛
Just trying to be accurate.
你說的對 這里是比公園好多了
You're right, this place is better than the park.
我錯了 不該讓你和我一樣被利用的
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have used you like I did.
我以為在外頭得到一點肯定就會感覺好些
I guess it just felt nice to get a little validation out there,
瞧 我知道還有比寫200字文章
and look, I know there are harder things
- 還難的事情 - 200 那可真多啊
- than writing a 200-word article. - 200? That's so many words.
謝謝 終于這家里有人懂我
Thank you. Finally someone in this family gets me.
我決定以后跟你探討我的問題
You know, I'm going to start coming to you with my problems.
你兒子喜歡氣球嗎
Would your son like a balloon?
哦 他不是我的兒子
Oh, he's not my son.
當然了 你這么年輕怎會有這么大的兒子
Oh, of course. You're too young to have a son his age.
給你媽發短信 接你回去
Text your mom to pick you up.
- 你在這里工作多久了 - 13年了
- So how long have you worked here? - Oh, 13 years.
這是我和大波波部落孩子的合照
Here I am with the children of the Grand Popo tribe.
他們寫了首關于我的歌
They wrote a song about me.
- 真棒啊 Mike - 實際上沒那么棒啦
- Wow. That's amazing, Mike. - It's really not that amazing.
他們給所有白人都唱那首歌
They sing that song to all the white people
好讓他們買他們的圍巾
to convince them to buy scarves.
- 還開那輛十萬刀的車 Harris - 事實上
- Still driving that $100,000 car, Harris? - Actually...
對 我記得當他第一次拿到那車
Yeah, I remember when he first got that car.
我就想 喔
I remember thinking, "Whoa,
Harris的中年危機來得也太早了
mid-life crisis comes early for Harris."
事實上 也不算太早
Well, actually, not that early.
雖然我們是朋友 但我還是會干掉你
You know, we might be friends, but I'll take you out.
- 不太難 - 嘿 是Leigh
- It's not that hard. - Oh, hey, it's Leigh.
她想讓我去JJ接Graham
I guess she wants us to pick up Graham at JJ's funcade.
好吧 抱歉 朋友們 今晚只能這樣了
Well, sorry, guys. I guess we've got to call it a night.
不過 Kelly和Harris不必到此為止
Well, Kelly and Harris don't have to call it a night.
我還能去喝一杯
I'm not going to say no to a drink.
你是我喜歡的類型
Oh, you are my kind of guy.
不然我們一起去JJ吧
I know. Why don't we all go to JJ's?
我們還可以玩一會
And we can play a little
滑雪球 然后給這大家伙來份烤玉米餅
skee-ball and get some nachos for the big fella.
- 你最好別這樣了 - 我想 我還是走吧
- You better stop that. - You know, I think I better get going.
明天我還要起早呢
I have an early morning tomorrow.
你愿意陪我一起上樓嗎
Do you want to walk me up upstairs?
別傻了 他完全不順路啊
Don't be silly. It's completely out of his way.
我陪你上樓
I'll walk you upstairs,
然后Annie和我順路帶Harris回家
and Annie and I will drop Harris off at home on our way.
也許明天再順路去JJ呢
And then maybe we could stop by JJ's tomorrow.
Mike 我們要去接我們兒子
Mike, we need to pick up our son.
你說的對 Annie
You're absolutely right, Annie.
你帶Kelly回家 然后回來
You should take Kelly home and then come back
掌控大局 Harris和我去接Graham
and man the nerve center, and Harris and I will go get Graham.
我一點也不想這么做
I don't want to do that at all.
不如這樣吧
Here's an out-of-the-box idea.
沒人送Kelly回家 因為她就住
Why doesn't nobody take Kelly home, 'cause she only lives
樓上 這里很安全 她很好
one floor up, and it's a safe building. And she'll be fine.
對吧 Annie Annie
Isn't that right, Annie? Annie?
你知道嗎 我樓上還有更多的勺子
You know, I have some more spoons upstairs.
鄭重聲明 不準摸我肚子
For the record, don't touch my belly.
現在 我先走了 我要上樓
Now, if you will excuse me, I'm going upstairs
穿著襯衫來一炮
to make love with my shirt on.
謝謝你在我腦子里留下這樣的畫面
Thank you for leaving me with that image.
Annie 還是我 Mike 你還在這兒嗎
Annie, it's Mike again. Are you still here?
因為這里我都轉了20分鐘了
'Cause I've been walking around for 20 minutes.
我現在渾身出汗在游樂場里晃悠
I'm a sweaty guy lurking around an arcade.
別人都快覺得我是變態了
People are starting to think I'm a creep.
嘿 你要走了嗎
Hey! Are you leaving?
- 是 - 你真就這樣走了啊
- Yeah. - You're seriously bailing?
- 因為Reese喜歡我 - 你這話說的真詭異
- Is this because Reese is into me? - That is mystifying.
只是她不是我想的那樣
She just isn't who I thought she was.
誰在乎呢 Reese不是女同又怎樣
Who cares? So Reese isn't a lesbian.
很抱歉 你沒能在你想要的朋友
I'm sorry that's not a box you can check off
單子上勾上一項
on your list of friends.
我喜歡獨一無二的朋友
I like having friends who are unique.
是 這樣你才感覺你是獨一無二的
Yeah, so you can feel unique.
為什么不只因為友誼而交朋友呢
Why not just have friends because they're your friends?
Annie Annie 我知道你在這兒
Annie. Annie, I know you're here somewhere.
聽著 你對的 我是對Kelly動了心
Look, you were right. I had a crush on Kelly.
- 是爸爸嗎 - 恐怕是
- Is that Dad? - I'm afraid so.
她有好看的鎖骨
She had these well-defined collarbones
雨天能盛水
that could hold water in the rain.
我都沒意識到我還喜歡這款
I didn't even know I was into that.
但是我不應該
But I never should have...
舔那個勺子
licked the spoon.
我就是那個時候陷進去了
I got caught up in the moment.
為什么聽起來這樣 我怎么了
Why do I sound like this? What's happening to me?
我是機器人嗎
Am I a robot?
好很多了
Oh, that's better.
說到哪兒了
Where was I?
- 說完了 但愿 - 等等 Annie 對不起
- Finished, hopefully. - Oh, wait. Annie, I'm sorry.
聽著 我一開始就停不下來了
Look, I just got started, and I couldn't stop.
Mike 我根本不在乎那些
Mike, I don't even care about that.
我是說 迷戀鎖骨太詭異了
I mean, the collarbone thing was weird,
但是 你今晚著什么魔了
but what got into you tonight?
我很抱歉 我
I'm sorry. I...
并不是因為我對Kelly動心這事兒
I just... it wasn't even that I had a crush on Kelly.
其實我是在意Kelly對我有意思
It was that Kelly had a crush on me.
我得了這個病后知道還有女人
It's just nice to know after all that's happened
- 覺得我有魅力 感覺挺好的 - 那我呢
- that women still find me attractive. - What about me?
- 我覺得你很有魅力啊 - 哦 那不算
- I think you're attractive. - Oh, well, that doesn't count.
我是說 你還能怎樣
I mean, what are you gonna do,
離開一個受人喜愛身患帕金森的主播嗎
leave the beloved newsman with Parkinson's?
好吧 要是這是你擔心的
Okay, if that's what you're worried about,
我是打算等你容貌逝去再離開你
I will leave you the minute your looks go.
謝謝你 謝謝
I'd appreciate that. Thank you.
看 你一晚都穿著這個嗎
Look... hey, have you been wearing this all night?
你看起來真美
You look amazing.
是啊 我一晚上都想吸引你注意
Yes, I've been trying to get you to notice all night.
我說過 你越看越美嗎
If I told you you were beautiful every time you looked beautiful,
我都無暇看別的了
I'd never have time for anything else.
說的真好聽
That would be fine with me.
有時候 生活里你會左顧右盼
Sometimes in life, you get turned around
忘了你是誰
and forget who you really are.
對不起 我誤以為你是女同
Sorry I thought you were a lesbian.
沒關系 我原來也以為你是
That's okay. I thought you were too.
哦 好棒 你們會親親嗎
Oh, boss! Are you guys gonna kiss?!
好在你的家人會在你身邊提醒你
Luckily, your family is there to remind you.
他們才是質疑你
They're the ones who challenge you
支持你的人
and support you
不管發生什么 愛你如初
and love you no matter what.
- 嘿 伙計們 - 啥事 寶貝
- Hey guys, guys... - What, sweetie?
爸爸不見了
We lost Dad.
噓噓
Shh, shh.
Mike Mike
Mike, Mike.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
他們也是用遙控小丑魚氣球
They're also the ones who will drive you crazy
逼瘋你的人
with remote control fish balloons.
Ian 把這東西弄走
Ian, get that thing out of here!
Ian
Ian...
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組